Guide to the Jim Graham papers, 1961-2015 MS2013
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jim Graham/Whitman-Walker Clinic records, 1973-1998; MS2013 Series 1
  - Affiliated organizations, 1986-1997; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 7
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS)- Consultive Meeting on HIV/AIDS, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - CSIS Working Group on Global HIV/AIDS, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - CSIS Working Group on Global HIV/AIDS, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Center for Substance Abuse Treatment, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Changing Face of HIV Disease Handbook, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Cherry Jublie Gala, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Choices", undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Circle 6 Boston- AIDS Action Council, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Cities Advocating Emergency AIDS Relief (CAEAR), undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Community Advisory Committee on Viatical Settlements, March, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Community Based Care for Persons with AIDS- AETNA, December, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Department of Human Services- Directory of Services, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Directory of AIDS Resources, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Directory of HIV/AIDS Related Services Pamphlet, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Agenda Project, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia's Comprehensive City Wide Response Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Board of Directors Booklet, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Community Health Care System Manual, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Financial Analysis Fiscal Year 1997, September 17 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Health Care Programs- loose papers 1, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Health Care Programs- loose papers 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Health Care Programs- loose papers 3, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Meeting Records, Memorandums, By-Laws, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Policy and Procedures, August, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Public Benefit Corporation- Financial Summary and PBC plans, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia General Hospital Public Benefit Corporation- loose papers; financial papers, future goals and plans, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals I, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals II, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Corporation Board of Directors Manual I, undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Corporation Board of Directors Manual II, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Board of Directors Appointment- Jim Graham, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation D.C.General Hospital Community Health Centers, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Executive Session Agenda, March, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Human Resources Policy and Procedures Manual DRAFT, September 5, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Human Resources Policy and Procedures Manual, September 16, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Organizational Plan, April 30, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Planning Session Agenda, March 2, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - District of Columbia Health and Hospitals Public Benefit Corporation Procurement Regulations, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Episcopal Caring Response to AIDS (ECRA)- Annual Report, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - "Evening with Marion Barry", undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - External Advisory Board- SEIU, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Gay Marriage Project, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Annual Reports, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club Banquet, May 9, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Gertrude Stein Democratic Club Banquet, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - "Global HIV/AIDS- A Strategy for U.S.Leadership", undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - "Good Intentions: A Report on Federal AIDS Prevention Programs" October 1, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Haring, Keith- Editions on Paper, 1982-1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Historic Preservation of Neighborhoods in Washington D.C., undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - HIV/AIDS Mental Health Services 1st Annual Report, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - HIV/AIDS Publications, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - HIV/AIDS Publications, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - HIV/AIDS Surveillance Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Hospice Care of the District of Columbia, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - International Conference on AIDS, Washington D.C., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - III International Conference on AIDS, Washington D.C., Final Program, June 1-5, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - IV International Conference on AIDS Exhibit Catalogue, Catalogue Face of AIDS, List of Participants, Second Announcement, June 12-16, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - V International Conference on AIDS Handbook and Certificate, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - VII International Conference on AIDS/ III STD World Conference, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 10th International Conference on AIDS, Japan, August, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - XI International Conference on AIDS, Vancouver, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - It's Not Easy film discussion guide and accompanying information, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Junior League, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - La Clinica de Pueblo, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Latino Coalition I, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Latino Coalition II, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Lamda Community Center, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Leadership Washington, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian and Gay Freedom Festival, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - [The] Manual for Targeted Intervention Research on Sexually Transmitted Illnesses for the setting of Commercial Sex, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Mautner Project- Annual Report, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - McCormack and Farrow Recruitment Project, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - McCormack Survey- National Survey of Executive Directors of AIDS Services Organizations and Gay and Lesbian Social Services, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Medicaid Reform and Managed Care- AIDS Action Foundation Report, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Metropolitan AIDS Services Coalition, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Washington Community AIDS Partnership Advisory Committee Meeting, September 12, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services, 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council By-Laws, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council Comprehensive AIDS Reporting and Evaluation System, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council- Meeting Minutes I, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council- Meeting Minutes II, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council Northern Virginia Planning District Commission, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Metropolitan Washington Regional HIV Health Services Planing Council Role Assessment Subcommittee Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Meyer Foundation Report: AIDS Prevention and Education in the Washington Area Community, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - NAMES Project Quilt, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - National AIDS Network, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - National AIDS Network Director's Evaluation, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - National AIDS Network Directory, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - National AIDS Network Organizational Update, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - National AIDS Network- Report to the Board, San Diego, California, November 11-12, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - National AIDS Network- Skills Building Conference Directory, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - National AIDS Network Work Plan, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - National AIDS Policy Office, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - National AIDS Strategy, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - NALGHC Institute, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - NALGHC Meeting, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - National Association of Community Health Centers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA) Booklet, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - National Association of People With AIDS (Manager's Retreat Report), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - National Council for International Health (NCIH), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Health Foundation (NGLHF) Combined Federal Campaign Application, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - National HIV Testing Day- "Take the Test, Take Control," June 27, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (NLGHA), undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (NLGHA), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (NLGHA) Board Meeting, San Juan, February 15- 17, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (NLGHA) 17th Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Health Association (NLGHA) San Francisco meeting, October 5- 10, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - National March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - National Skills Building Conference, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - "New Hopes, New Challenges (Tony Keenam, Harkness Fellowship),", 1997 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Office of National AIDS Policy, "Regional Community Briefings on HIV/AIDS," December, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Organizations (Brother, Help Thyself), undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Organizational Study for AMFAR, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Pan-American Health Organization (PAHO), 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - People of Color Committee Report, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Prevention and Beyond I, August 13-17, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Prevention and Beyond II, August 13-17, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Pride Day, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Project Face to Face, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Proposal to Conduct an AIDS Health Promotion Risk Reduction Program for Groups at High Risk for AIDS, March 12, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Report of the Presidential Commission on HIV, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco General Hospital Comprehensive Care of the AIDS Patient: A Workshop, September 19-20, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Shanti Project Personnel Policies, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Strategies for Hospitals Regarding AIDS, September, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Treatment Improvement Protocol, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Department of Health Resources Administration Handbook I, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Department of Health Resources Administration Handbook II, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - U.S. General Accounting Office- Report: "AIDS Forecasting", 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - U.S. International Strategy on HIV/AIDS, July, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Venereal Disease Facts in the District of Columbia, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Vista, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Volunteer Activist Awards, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Washington Area Consortium on HIV Infection in Youth- Annual Report, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - White House Conference on HIV and AIDS, December 6, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Ward Conference- ADASA, undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Why We Stopped Doing Primary Prevention for Gay Men in 1985," from AIDS and Public Policy Journal, Vol.10, No.1, Winter, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - World AIDS Day, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Washington HIV Newsletter, Vol.1, No.2, February 6, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 22nd Annual Miss Gay Universe Ball, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1997; MS2013 Series 1 Subseries 8
    This subseries contains materials from the Whitman-Walker Clinic that could not be placed in any of the other series. Items include two issues of Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences and information regarding Philadelphia-DC AIDS Rides and Washington DC AIDS Rides. The majority of items in the series are located in scrapbook folders, which mostly contain news-clippings about the Whitman-Walker Clinic, AIDS, and gay and lesbian issues. The materials in this series date from 1973-97.
    - African American Civil War Memorial Freedom Foundation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Awards, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Beethoven Society 13th Anniversary Souvenir Program, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [The] Best of Washington Social Club, Inc. 1989 Watergate Affair Alice Awards Show and Presentations, 15th Anniversary 1974-1989, April 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Certificate of Appreciation, December, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Christmas Greeting Cards, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Crew Club, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - District of Columbia AIDS Cases by Ward (Zone) Statistics, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Cards, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - HealthQuest Magazine, May/June, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Living With AIDS Part 1, Spring, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Journal of the American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Living With AIDS Part 2, Summer, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Loose Papers- Proposed Agenda Community AIDS Advisory Committee; DC General Hospital Fax; Arent Fox letter, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Max Robinson Center- Coming Together on World AIDS Day, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous I, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous II, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous III, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous IV, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous V, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Outweek Magazine, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia- DC AIDS Ride Presented by Tanqueray, Print Media Summary Volume 1, October 8, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia- DC AIDS Ride Presented by Tanqueray, Electronic Media Summary Volume 1, October 8, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Poem, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Safe Sex Packet (Women), undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Scrapbook, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Scrapbook, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Scrapbook, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Scrapbook, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook I, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Scrapbook II, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook III, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook I, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook II, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook III, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook IV, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook Administrator's Copy I, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook Administrator's Copy II, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Scrapbook n.d., undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Scrapbook- Poland, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Washington DC AIDS Ride Presented by Tanqueray, Electronic Media Summary, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Washington DC AIDS Ride Presented by Tanqueray, Print Media Summary, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - White House Correspondence, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Polly Shackleton Campaign Button, Circa 1974 (Box 2A, Folder 1)
- Jim Graham/D.C. Council records, 1961-2015; 1998-2014; MS2013 Series 2
  The Jim Graham records contains material relating to the work of Jim Graham during his time as a District of Columbia City Council member, as well as his first campaign for Ward 1 Representative in 1998 and his re-election campaigns until 2014 when he was defeated and lost his seat. It is comprised of correspondence, flyers, publications, and other relevant materials
  Arranged into five subseries: Records, Public Engagement materials, Photographs, Oversized, and Campaign materials.
  - Records, 1961-2015; 1998-2014; Series 2 Subseries 1
    This subseries is arranged by topic, starting with materials created by and directly related to Jim Graham. The remainder of the series is then arranged alphabetically.
    - Council-related correspondence, 1999 August - 2000 May; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 1)
    - Council-related correspodence, 2004-2013; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence [1/2], 2002-2015, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence [2/2], 2002-2015, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 4)
    - Jim Graham Council office, 1999-2001, 2004-2005, 2012, 2014; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 5)
    - Ward One Elections, 2002, 2006, 2009-2010, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Council Swearing In Ceremony programs, 2001, 2005, 2011, 2013; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 7)
    - D.C. Council publications, 1993-1994, 1999-2000, 2008; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 8)
    - District of Columbia history materials, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 9)
    - Wilson Building History, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 10)
    - Development and preservation projects, 1995, 2004, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 6A, Folder 11)
    - Campaign finance and Board of Elections, 2002, 2005, 2009; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 1)
    - Campaign finance, 1998-2004; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 2)
    - Campaign finance [1/2], 2006-2008, 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 3)
    - Campaign finance [2/2], 2006-2008, 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 4)
    - Conflict of interest, 1999, 2002; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Government offices, 1999, 2002, 2004-2006; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 6)
    - Office of General Counsel, 2011-2012; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 7)
    - Washington Area Metropolitan Transit Authority (WMATA), 2008-2009; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 8)
    - Youth Programs and the DC Children and Youth Investment Trust Corporation (CYITC), 2002; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 9)
    - Youth Programs and the DC Children and Youth Investment Trust Corporation (CYITC), 2000, 2007, 2009-2012; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 7A, Folder 10)
    - Carlos Rosario International Public Charter School, 2013-2014; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 1)
    - Citizens for Jeff Smith, 2011-2012; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 2)
    - Charles Brodsky [1/2], 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 3)
    - Charles Brodsky [2/2], 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 4)
    - Elizabeth Taylor, 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 5)
    - Howard Theatre Restoration Project, 2009-2010; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 6)
    - Keely Thompson, 2009-2013; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 7)
    - RFK Stadium and Nationals Stadium, 1961, 2004-2005; 2004-2005; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 8)
    - Ted Loza, 2011; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 9)
    - Wanda's Hair Studio, 2012; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 8A, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign and D.C. Council materials, 1996-1998, 2001-2002; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Council campaigns, 1998-2014; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Council campaigns, 2000, 2010, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Council campaigns [1/2], 2006, 2010, 2014, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous D.C. Council campaigns [2/2], 2006, 2010, 2014, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Council, 2003, 2007, 2009-2010, 2013; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 6)
    - Citizen Complaint Reports, 1999; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1997-1999, 2006-2008, 2010, 2012, 2015; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 9A, Folder 8)
    - Poster: "Graham is a clown"/"Graham es un payaso", undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 14A, Folder 1)
    - CD-ROM: Miscellaneous, 2014, undated; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 14A, Folder 2)
  - Public Engagement materials, 1998-2012; Series 2 Subseries 2
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains materials relating to Jim Graham's personal and professional life from 1998-2012. This includes Graham's time as councilmember for Ward 1 for the District of Columbia and as chairman of the Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority's board of directors.
    - Personal Planner I, 1998 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
    - Personal Planner II, 1999 (Box 1A, Folder 3)
    - Personal Planner III, 1999 (Box 1A, Folder 4)
    - Personal Planner IV, 2000 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
    - Personal Planner V, 2001 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
    - Metro Weekly - Person of the Year: Jim Graham, 1998 December 31 (Box 2A, Folder 2)
    - Federal City Council, 1999 April (Box 2A, Folder 3)
    - Metro 2001 Calendar (Box 2A, Folder 4)
    - The Financier, 2003 July-August (Box 2A, Folder 5)
    - DVD: Nightline - Bearing Witness, 2004 February 20 (Box 2A, Folder 6)
    - Fort Totten Memorial Service - speeches and program, 2010 June 22 (Box 2A, Folder 7)
    - The Lancet, 2012 July (Box 2A, Folder 8)
    - CD-ROM: AIDS 2012 Informational Media (2 discs) (Box 2A, Folder 9)
    - AIDS 2012 Informational Handouts (Box 2A, Folder 10)
    - AIDS 2012 Programme Supplement (Box 2A, Folder 11)
    - AIDS 2012 Programme (Box 2A, Folder 12)
    - Dedication and Memorial Ceremony programs, 2012-2015; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 14A, Folder 3)
    - CD-ROM: The Dalai Lama's Visit to Booker T. Washington Public Charter School, audio program, 2005 November 10; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14A, Folder 4)
    - DVD: Calvin Larone Woodland's Homegoing Service, 2010 February 2; MS2013 Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 14A, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, 1998-2014; Series 2 Subseries 3
    This subseries consists of photographs, both personal and professional, relating to Jim Graham's time as a D.C. City Council member.
    - Photos: WMATA, 1999 September 15 (Box 3A, Folder 6)
    - Photos: Adam's Morgan Day, 2001 December (Box 3A, Folder 7)
    - Photos: Jim Graham and Friends, 2002 July 24 (Box 3A, Folder 8)
    - Photos: Jim Graham, Grace Ridgley and Friends, 2008-2009 (Box 3A, Folder 9)
    - Photos: Christmas Party, 2010 (Box 3A, Folder 10)